# H. T. Premachandra

I am a hardworking, motivated and a passionate individual with a proven track record as a Management Assistant for the past 2.5 years. I always strive to achieve the highest standard possible, at any given task and in any situation. As a self-motivated and trust worthy individual I could work in any circumstance either as a part of a team or with minimal supervision



tharindulivingcl@gmail.com



071 26 46 495



279/a, Gedabaduwa Road, Kindelpitiya, Welmilla, Bandaragama



06 May, 1993

### **SKILLS & SPECIALTIES**

Computer Applications
Proficiency (MS windows,
office, outlook, teams etc.)

Strong Language & Communications Skills

Hardworking and Self Motivated

Multi Tasker

Quick Learner

#### LANGUAGES

**English** 

Full professional proficiency

Sinhala

Full professional proficiency

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Built a personal portfolio/webpage to display my profile online 2019

https://tharindu01.github.io/tharindu

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Management Assistant

Telecommunications Regulatory Commission of Sri Lanka 06/2019 - 12/2021

#### Sales Consultant

Ceylinco Life Insurance Company Ltd 07/2014 - 03/2015

#### **EDUCATION**

## Diploma in English

Aquinas College of Higher Studies 2015 - 2016

# General Certificate of Education (Advanced Level)

Bandaragama National School 2012

English - A
 Economics - B
 Business Studies - B
 Accounting - C

# General Certificate of Education (Ordinary Level)

Bandaragama National School 2009

English - A Buddhism - A Mathematics - B Health & Phy. Studies - A - C Citizenship Education - B History - S Sinhala - C Science **English Literature** - S

#### OTHER INFORMATION

# **Bachelor of Information Technology**

University of Colombo – (External)

Not yet completed